export const chapter = "Chapter - 7: Sentence";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question: "What is a sentence?",
          optionA: "A collection of words with random arrangement",
          optionB: "A group of words that makes complete sense",
          optionC: "A sequence of words with reversed order",
          correctAnswer: "B",
        },
        {
          question: "Which characteristic is essential for a sentence?",
          optionA: "Random word arrangement",
          optionB: "Meaningful arrangement of facts",
          optionC: "Lengthy structure",
          correctAnswer: "B",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the term for a sentence that declares or states something?",
          optionA: "Interrogative Sentence",
          optionB: "Imperative Sentence",
          optionC: "Assertive Sentence",
          correctAnswer: "C",
        },
        {
          question: "What type of questions are Yes/No-type questions?",
          optionA: "Interrogative Questions",
          optionB: "Wh-type Questions",
          optionC: "Exclamatory Questions",
          correctAnswer: "A",
        },
        {
          question: "Which type of sentence expresses an order or request?",
          optionA: "Exclamatory Sentence",
          optionB: "Interrogative Sentence",
          optionC: "Imperative Sentence",
          correctAnswer: "C",
        },
        {
          question:
            "How can an assertive sentence be transformed into a negative sentence?",
          optionA: "By adding question words",
          optionB: "By reversing the word order",
          optionC: "By inserting no/not/never if there is an auxiliary",
          correctAnswer: "C",
        },
        {
          question: "What is the purpose of exclamatory sentences?",
          optionA: "To express orders",
          optionB: "To ask questions",
          optionC: "To express strong or sudden feelings",
          correctAnswer: "C",
        },
        {
          question: "How can a sentence containing 'too' be transformed?",
          optionA: "By changing the order of words",
          optionB: "By using 'so' and expressing a result",
          optionC: "By adding more words",
          correctAnswer: "B",
        },
        {
          question:
            "How can an exclamatory sentence 'How beautiful the rain is!' be transformed into an assertive sentence?",
          optionA: "The rain is very beautiful.",
          optionB: "The rain is not beautiful.",
          optionC: "Is the rain beautiful?",
          correctAnswer: "A",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What type of sentence expresses a wish or unreal condition?",
          optionA: "Interrogative Sentence",
          optionB: "Exclamatory Sentence",
          optionC: "Imperative Sentence",
          correctAnswer: "B",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blanks:",
    questions: [
        {
          question: "A sentence is a group of words that makes ____________.",
          optionA: "Incomplete sense",
          optionB: "Random arrangement",
          optionC: "Complete sense",
          correctAnswer: "C",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In an interrogative sentence, questions can be of two types: Yes/No-type questions and ____________ questions.",
          optionA: "Assertive",
          optionB: "Exclamatory",
          optionC: "Wh-type",
          correctAnswer: "C",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Imperative sentences are sentences that can give ____________ or request something.",
          optionA: "Commands",
          optionB: "Statements",
          optionC: "Questions",
          correctAnswer: "A",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Exclamatory sentences express ____________ or sudden feelings.",
          optionA: "Orders",
          optionB: "Strong",
          optionC: "Questions",
          correctAnswer: "B",
        },
        {
          question:
            "When transforming an assertive sentence into a negative sentence, 'no/not/never' is inserted if there is an ____________.",
          optionA: "Exclamation",
          optionB: "Auxiliary",
          optionC: "Interrogative",
          correctAnswer: "B",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In Wh-type questions, the question word is put at the beginning, followed by ____________, subject, and verb.",
          optionA: "Object",
          optionB: "Comma",
          optionC: "Auxiliary verb",
          correctAnswer: "C",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Exclamatory sentences can be transformed into assertive sentences by expressing the exclamation in a more ____________ manner.",
          optionA: "Emotional",
          optionB: "Complicated",
          optionC: "Simple",
          correctAnswer: "A",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The introduction of English education in India led to a decline in traditional ____________.",
          optionA: "Cuisine",
          optionB: "Values",
          optionC: "Clothing",
          correctAnswer: "B",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The British educational system in India had limitations, especially in neglecting mass education, particularly in ____________ areas.",
          optionA: "Urban",
          optionB: "Rural",
          optionC: "Suburban",
          correctAnswer: "B",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Transforming an exclamatory sentence into an assertive one involves expressing the exclamation in a more ____________ manner.",
          optionA: "Confused",
          optionB: "Complex",
          optionC: "Straightforward",
          correctAnswer: "C",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
        {
          question: "A sentence is a group of words that makes complete sense.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "Imperative sentences express strong or sudden feelings.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Interrogative sentences include Yes/No-type questions and Wh-type questions.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Exclamatory sentences can be transformed into assertive sentences by expressing the exclamation in a more emotional manner.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The introduction of English education in India led to an emphasis on traditional values.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the Hindu system of education, ashrams were often built and organized by wealthy landowners.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the Muslim education system, students often practiced rote learning.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The British officials like William Jones and Colebrook believed that ancient Indian knowledge should be excluded from the new educational system.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Charter Act of 1813 provided an annual grant for introducing English education in India, leading to the Oriental-Occidental Controversy about the choice of Arabic as the medium of instruction.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Sir Charles Wood's Despatch of 1854 emphasized the diffusion of European knowledge in India.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
      ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
